Some of the common mistakes you may experience while learning how to ollie higher, and learning how to ollie up onto different heights, is probably going to have to do with the coordination that's needed with the pop and the jump.
What's you're going to find is a lot of times, you're going to hang up on your way up.
This is very common mistake, so basically what happens is, when you ollie up, as you're headed upward, your back truck, especially this part of your truck, right here, is going to hook up, on the top of the surface, and hang, and cause you to get thrown forward.
So what you want to do is, you want to make sure that you can ollie high enough to get onto whatever you're getting onto.
And after that, it's just going to be trial and error.
So, the most common mistake is getting hooked up.
The other common mistake, maybe, is just ollieing up too high, and coming down all wrong, and not being able to control your board.
This is just one of the common mistakes that happens when you're trying something new, or you're rolling a little too fast.
So, what you want to do is, take it slowly at your own pace, and figure these things out as you go along.
And, also remember, that now that you're ollieing up something higher, you're going to have to adjust your foot placement, so, further back, more foot on the tip of the tail, and much more jumping, and figuring out how to coordinate all this stuff together, and that's going to help you ollie higher.